RG 001:001, Records of the Colony of Connecticut
Connecticut State Library
Records of the Colony of Connecticut
1636-1776
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut
11 volumes
The official record books of the General Court/General Assembly, containing proceedings and other materials.
RG001_001
T002508
Scope and Content
The official record books of the General Court/General Assembly, containing proceedings and other materials.
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically in volumes numbered 1-11. These volumes are also numbered 1-11 within the larger collection of Early General Records (EGR).
Bibliography
Books
Hinman, Royal Ralph, ed. Letters from the English kings and queens, Charles II, James II, William and Mary, Anne, George II, &c...1635-1749. Hartford: John B. Eldridge, 1836..
Index Terms
Subjects:
Connecticut -- History -- Colonial period, ca. 1600-1775 -- Sources; Connecticut -- History -- Revolution, 1775-1783 -- Sources; Connecticut -- Politics and government -- To 1775 -- Sources; Connecticut -- Politics and government -- 1775-1783 -- Sources; Connecticut -- Politics and government -- Sources; Connecticut -- History -- Sources; Wills -- Connecticut
Alternate Creator:
Connecticut. Council; Connecticut. General Assembly
Restrictions on Access
Researchers should first consult use copies when available. See Alternate Form Available Section below.
See the policy.
Alternative Form Available
Microfilmed as part of. Volumes 1-3 are on Conn A.6 Reel 1; Volumes 4-5 are on Conn A.6 Reel 2; Volumes 6-7 are on Conn A.6 Reel 3; Volume 8-9 are on Conn A.6 Rell 4; Volumes 10-11 are on Conn A.6 Reel 5.
Published as Available online through.
Inventory
- Records, 1636-1776
  See Restrictions on Access note above
  - 1636-1649 (Volume 1 / 1)
    Includes probate records circa 1635-1650.
  - 1649-1669 (Volume 2 / 2)
    The Code of 1650 is in Vol.2, middle of page 6, upside down in the back of the volume.
  - 1670-1709 (Volume 3 / 3)
  - 1706-1715 (Volume 4 / 4)
  - 1715-1729 (Volume 5 / 5)
    Part 1, pages 1-372.
  - 1715-1729 (Volume 5 / 5A)
    Part 2, pages 373-735.
  - 1730-1739 (Volume 6 / 6)
  - 1740-1749 (Volume 7 / 7)
  - 1750-1757 (Volume 8 / 8)
  - 1752-1762 (Volume 9 / 9)
  - 1762-1770 (Volume 10 / 10)
  - 1771-1776 (Volume 11 / 11)